this video will introduce you to the
该视频将向您介绍
revenue equivalence theorem which is one
收益等价定理之一
of the most important results in Option
Option中最重要的结果
theory I'll begin by stating the theorem
理论，我将从阐述定理开始
and explaining why it's important I'll
并解释为什么这很重要
show how we can use it to think about
展示我们如何使用它来思考
first price auctions and then at the end
首先进行价格拍卖，然后结束
of the video I'll prove the theorem to
视频中，我将证明定理
you which is important because there's
你很重要，因为有
actually a lot we can learn from the way
实际上，我们可以从中学习很多
that the proof works so to begin what is
证明有效，所以开始什么是
this revenue equivalence theorem well
这个收入等价定理很好
most importantly it's an answer to the
最重要的是，这是对
question of which auction we should
我们应该进行哪种拍卖的问题
choose so far we've seen all kinds of
选择到目前为止，我们已经看到了各种各样的
different auctions first price auctions
不同的拍卖第一次价格拍卖
second price English Dutch it's kind of
第二个价格是英语荷兰语
confusing you wonder how you should
令您感到困惑的是您应该如何
actually as an auctioneer decide which
实际上作为拍卖师决定
auction you should use well strangely
拍卖你应该很好地使用
enough the revenue equivalence theorem
足够的收入等价定理
says that to a large extent it actually
说在很大程度上
doesn't matter which one you pick so
选哪一个都没关系
let's see formally what it says let's
让我们正式看看它说了什么
assume that we have n different
假设我们有n个不同
risk-neutral agents each of whom has an
风险中立的代理人，每个人都有一个
independent private valuation for the
的独立私人估值
single good that's at auction and each
拍卖中的单个商品
of which is drawn from a cumulative
其中从累计
distribution F now we're going to
分布F现在我们要
consider two different auction
考虑两个不同的拍卖
mechanisms for these two similar
这两个相似的机制
settings and we want to assume two
设置，我们要假设两个
things about these auction mechanisms
关于这些拍卖机制的事情
first of all that in equilibrium they
首先，它们处于平衡状态
allocate the good in the same way all of
以相同的方式分配商品
the time so for all of the different
对于所有不同的时间
types that agents might actually have
代理商可能实际拥有的类型
they have the same allocations and
他们有相同的分配
secondly that an agent with valuation 0
其次是一个估价为0的代理商
an agent with the lowest possible type
具有最低可能类型的代理
would have an expected utility of 0 in
预期效用为0 in
the auction if these two properties hold
如果这两个属性成立，则进行拍卖
across both of these auctions then the
在这两次拍卖中
revenue equivalence theorem tells us
收入等价定理告诉我们
that both auctions yield the same
两次拍卖产生相同的结果
expected revenue and indeed that both
预期收入，实际上两者
result in any bitter with the same
导致任何痛苦相同
valuation making the same expected
估值与预期相同
payment so in other words as long as two
也就是说，只要两个
mechanisms allocate in the same way and
机制分配方式相同，
as long as they charge an agent with the
只要他们向代理商收取
lowest possible valuation the same
最低可能的估价不变
amount 0 then the rest of their payment
金额0，然后其余的付款
functions have to be the same as well so
功能也必须一样
you can't get extra money out of agents
你不能从代理商那里得到额外的钱
without changing the
不改变
ocation function or the payment of the
定位功能或支付
low estate valued agent now in fact I've
实际上，我现在已经拥有低房地产价值的经纪人
stated the revenue equivalence theorem
陈述了收入等价定理
here in a way that's a bit narrower than
在某种程度上比
I have to just to make it a bit easier
我只需要使其变得容易一点
to say to you so in fact I can get
跟你说，实际上我可以
beyond the independent private values
超越独立的私人价值观
assumption that I've made and I can also
我所做的假设，我也可以
get a bit beyond the single good
超越单一的好处
assumption
假设
so stating it in its full generality
如此概括地说
would have been just a little bit more
本来应该多一点
notationally clumsy although the proof
尽管证明
that I'll give you actually holds more
我会给你更多
generally okay now let's see why the
现在基本上可以了，让我们看看为什么
revenue equivalence theorem is useful
收益等价定理很有用
for thinking about first and second
考虑第一和第二
price options to do this we need to
为此的价格选择，我们需要
think about a concept called the caithe
想一想叫caithe的概念
order statistic of a distribution
分布的顺序统计
so the keith's order statistic is the
所以基思的订单统计量是
expected value of the K largest of n
n的K最大的期望值
draws so imagine that I was to
如此想象，我曾经
independently draw five times from a
从一个独立绘制五次
distribution what is the expected value
分配的期望值是多少
of the biggest of those draws or what is
这些抽奖中最大的一次是什么
the expected value of the second-biggest
第二大的期望值
of those drugs those are questions about
在那些药物中，有关于
the first order and second order
一阶和二阶
statistics of that distribution for K
K的分布统计
equals one and two and for N equals five
等于一和二，对于N等于五
well here's a useful formula to know for
好吧，这是一个有用的公式
for what we're gonna think about just
对于我们要考虑的只是
now if I make n I IAD which which is to
现在，如果我使n IIAD到
say independent and identically
独立且相同地说
distributed draws from the uniform
从制服分发抽奖
distribution over the range zero to
分布范围从零到
v-max the caithe order statistic is what
v-max caithe订单统计量是多少
you see here it's this fraction
你看这里就是这个分数
multiplied by V Max
乘以V Max
now using this fact directly I can
现在直接使用这个事实，我可以
conclude that in a second price auction
得出结论，在第二次价格拍卖中
the sellers expected revenue is this
卖方期望的收入是这个
fraction and that's because I know that
分数，因为我知道
in a second price auction the seller's
在第二次价格拍卖中，卖方的
expected revenue is the same as the
预期收入与
expected value of the second highest
第二高的期望值
bidder
投标人
because the seller always gets the
因为卖方总是得到
expected revenue always gets the revenue
预期收入总能获得收入
of the second highest bid in a second
一秒钟内第二高的出价
price auction so if I just substitute in
价格拍卖，所以，如果我只是替代
that's this is the expression that I get
这就是我得到的表达
and you can confirm that now first and
您现在可以先确认
second price auctions both satisfy the
第二价格拍卖都满足
requirements of the revenue equivalence
收入等值的要求
theorem it's easy to see for second
定理很容易看出来
price auctions for first price auctions
首次拍卖的价格拍卖
it's not quite as easy to see that they
看到他们并不容易
allocate goods in the same way but as
以相同的方式分配货物，但
the second price auction does but
第二次价格拍卖会
basically what I want to reason is that
基本上我想说的是
in a first price auction the bidder with
在第一次价格拍卖中，投标人
the highest value gets the good and I
最高的价值得到好处，我
can argue this essentially by saying
基本上可以说
every symmetric game has a symmetric
每个对称游戏都有一个对称
equilibrium a the first price auction
平衡第一次价格拍卖
Bayesian game is a symmetric game
贝叶斯游戏是对称游戏
because everyone's iid and so in a
因为每个人都在玩，所以
symmetric equilibrium of this game a
该游戏的对称平衡a
higher valuation is gonna happen if and
如果和
only if a bidder has a higher bid and
仅当投标人具有更高的出价并且
that's gonna mean that the person with
那意味着那个人
the highest valuation wins the auction
最高估价赢得拍卖
so then I conclude that a bidder in a
因此，我得出结论：
first price auction is going to have to
第一次价格拍卖将不得不
pay on expectation the same amount as
期望支付与
the same bidder would pay on expectation
相同的投标人将按预期支付
in a second price auction and because
在第二次价格拍卖中，因为
only the winner has to pay anything in a
只有获胜者必须在
first price auction that means everyone
第一次价格拍卖意味着每个人
should bid they're expected payment
应该出价他们期望的付款
conditional on being the winner of a
以成为某人的获胜者为条件
second price auction so each bidder in a
第二次价格拍卖，因此
first price auction should imagine that
第一次价格拍卖应该想象
they're the highest bidder and then bid
他们是出价最高的人，然后出价
the expected second highest bid
预期第二高的出价
conditional and their value being the
有条件的，其价值是
highest sample from the distribution and
分布中的最高样本
you might think this is kind of strange
您可能会认为这有点奇怪
because of all of the N bidders n minus
因为所有N个竞标者n减
one of them will be wrong when they do
其中之一会做错
this conditioning only one of them
这种条件只是其中之一
actually
其实
we'll be the highest bidder so why
我们将成为出价最高的人，为什么
should they all bid as though they think
他们是否都应该像他们认为的那样出价
they're the highest bidder well the
他们是出价最高的人
reason this makes sense is that the only
之所以有意义是因为
bidder that this matters to is the
重要的竞标者是
bidder with the highest valuation and so
估价最高的竞标者等等
if the bidder turns out in fact to win
如果竞标者实际上胜出
the first price auction then he was
第一次价格拍卖，然后他是
right to do this conditioning and
进行此调节的权利，以及
otherwise his bid doesn't matter anyway
否则，他的出价无所谓
and so the fact that he conditioned rung
因此，他对梯级进行调节
is okay so so thinking now about the
没关系，所以现在考虑
highest bidder if his valuation VI is
最高出价者，如果他的估值VI为
the high value then there are n minus 1
高值则有n减1
other values which are below his and so
其他低于他的值等等
all he knows is that they're drawn from
他只知道他们是从
the uniform distribution on the interval
间隔上的均匀分布
between zero and his bid I hear I'm
在零到他的出价之间我听说我
thinking about first price options in
考虑中的第一个价格选择
the case of a uniform distribution and
均匀分布的情况下
thus the expected value of the second
因此第二个的期望值
highest bid is going to be the first
最高出价将是第一个
order statistic of n minus 1 draws from
n的阶次统计量减去1得出
this distribution we're thinking about
我们正在考虑的分布
the second highest bid but we've
第二高的出价，但我们已经
conditioned on the first highest bid so
以第一高的出价为条件
we're now going to think about the
我们现在要考虑
biggest of the draws among the remaining
在其余的最大抽奖
agents that's going to be the second
代理商将是第二个
highest bit and I can just substitute in
最高的位，我可以替代
to this expression for the the expected
对于预期的此表达式
for the first order statistic of n minus
对于n减的一阶统计量
1 draws and I can substitute in n minus
1次平局，我可以负n替代
1 into that expression and simplify and
1表示该表达式，并简化和
what I get is this expression here and
我得到的是这里的表达，
that's something you've seen before
那是你以前见过的东西
right we've claimed in the past that the
是的，我们过去声称
symmetric equilibrium of a first price
第一价格的对称均衡
auction is with the independent uniform
拍卖是与独立制服
valuations is for all of the bidders to
估值适用于所有投标人
bid n minus 1 over n times their
出价n减去n的1倍
valuation and now you can see actually
估值，现在您可以实际看到
where that comes from that we can
从那里我们可以
actually find that by reasoning through
实际上通过推理来发现
revenue equivalents so so essentially
收入等值从本质上讲是如此
there's two ways of finding the
有两种方法可以找到
equilibrium of an auction like a first
像第一次拍卖一样的均衡拍卖
price auction the hard way is that you
价格拍卖的难点在于你
do a ton of calculus to actually figure
进行大量演算以实际计算
out what the equilibrium is from first
从一开始就得出均衡是什么
principles that's really hard even in
即使在
the case of a first price auction that
在第一次价格拍卖的情况下
that's really hard the easy way is that
这真的很难，简单的方法是
you guess the equilibrium by appealing
你通过吸引来猜测平衡
to revenue equivalence and then you just
到收入等值，然后
verify that it's an equilibrium and so
验证这是一个平衡，所以
we know from revenue equivalence by
我们从等价收入中知道
comparing to second price auctions that
与第二次拍卖相比
are easy to
很容易
analyze that the expected revenue has to
分析预期收入必须
be the same and then we work through to
一样，然后我们努力
figure out how bidders would have to bid
弄清楚投标者将如何投标
to get that expected revenue and we
获得预期的收入，我们
arrive at this expression okay well all
到达这个表情好吧
that remains for this video is for me to
这部影片剩下的就是我
show you how we prove the revenue
向您展示我们如何证明收入
equivalence theorem so let me now do
等价定理，让我现在做
that this is going to be the most
这将是最
technical and advanced part of the video
视频的技术和高级部分
if you find that you bogged down and
如果您发现自己陷入困境，
this is too much for you you understand
这对您来说太多了
everything else you need to know about
您需要了解的所有其他信息
revenue equivalence without watching the
收入等值而不看
proof so you can stop watching the video
证明，以便您可以停止观看视频
now but I encourage you to go on because
现在，但我鼓励您继续，因为
I think this is a really cool proof
我认为这是一个很酷的证明
actually I actually worked really hard
其实我真的很努力
to make this part of the video for you
为您制作视频的这一部分
because I really like this proof so I
因为我真的很喜欢这个证明，所以我
hope you enjoy it too so so let's see
希望你也喜欢，所以让我们看看
how it works we have to introduce the
如何运作，我们必须介绍
idea of an X interim allocation function
X临时分配函数的构想
and an X interim payment so let's see
和X期中付款，让我们来看一下
what that means well I'm going to call
那意味着我要打电话给我
remember we have this choice function ax
记得我们有这个选择功能的斧头
well I'm now going to have the choice
好吧，我现在要选择
function X I and what I'm going to mean
函数XI以及我的意思
by that is the choice function from the
通过那是来自
point of view of agent I given that
我给出的代理的观点
everybody else is following the
其他人都在关注
equilibrium strategy profile asks for
均衡策略简介
some base nash equilibrium and that age
一些基础纳什均衡和那个年龄
and i has type VI so what this X I is
我有VI型，所以这个XI是什么
going to give us is the probability that
要给我们的是
an agent I with type VI is going to be
我拥有VI型的特工
allocated the good given that everybody
分配给每个人的好处
follows the equilibrium strategy s
遵循均衡策略
including I and similarly P sub I is
包括我和类似的P sub I是
going to be the expected payment that
将是预期的付款
agent AI has to make again under the
代理商AI必须根据
assumption that everyone is following
假设每个人都在关注
the equilibrium strategy profile s and
均衡策略配置文件s和
that agent I has type VI so here's a
那个代理商我有VI型，所以这是一个
stronger theorem than the revenue
比收益更强的定理
equivalence theorem but it should be
等价定理，但应该是
easy to see that this implies the
显而易见，这意味着
revenue equivalence theorem directly so
收入等价定理直接这样
once we have this theorem we we just
一旦有了这个定理，我们就
basically get the revenue equivalence
基本取得收入等值
theorem for free what the revenue
免费定理是什么收益
equivalence theorem tells us is that
等价定理告诉我们，
mechanisms that allocate in the same way
以相同方式分配的机制
all have to have the same pain
所有人都必须有同样的痛苦
function what this tells us is exactly
函数告诉我们的正是
what the payment function has to be a
付款功能必须是什么
little bit about how the allocation has
关于分配的一点点
to work as well it really shows us
很好地工作，这确实向我们展示了
exactly what the equilibrium even needs
均衡甚至需要什么
to be and so as a side effect we'll see
作为副作用，我们将看到
that
那
that any two mechanisms that allocate in
在其中分配的任何两种机制
the same way I have to have the same
同样，我必须拥有相同的方式
payments but let's look at what this
付款，但让我们看看这是什么
theorem says this is really kind of
定理说这真的是
crucial theorem for mechanism design so
机构设计的关键定理
here we're saying that when values are
这里我们说的是当价值是
drawn from a continuous Joint
取自连续关节
Distribution F and agents are
分布F和代理商是
risk-neutral a strategy profile s is in
风险中立的策略配置文件
Bayes Nash equilibrium only if the two
仅当贝叶斯纳什均衡
conditions that follow are true for all
以下条件对所有人都适用
agents I first of all we need
我首先需要的代理商
monotonicity so each agents X interim
单调性，因此每个代理X临时
allocation probability needs to be
分配概率需要为
monotone non-decreasing in that agents
该代理中的单调非减少
value so in other words as agents have
价值，换句话说，就是代理
higher and higher values for the good
物品的价值越来越高
their probability of getting the good
他们获得利益的可能性
averaged across all of the other agents
所有其他代理商的平均值
type as well as potentially across
类型以及潜在的跨度
randomness in the mechanism itself needs
机制本身需要随机性
to weakly increase so as I have higher
弱增长，因为我有更高
and higher values for the good it can
和更高的价值，它可以
never reduce my chance on average of
永远不会减少我的机会
getting the good so that's necessary for
得到好处，所以对于
a base Nash equilibrium the other thing
基本的纳什均衡
that's necessary for a business
这对企业来说是必要的
equilibrium is the following payment
均衡是以下支付
identity and this probably looks kind of
身份，这可能看起来有点
scary it's just a whole lot of math
可怕的是很多数学
right so I'm saying the payment function
对，所以我说的是付款功能
this.x interim expected payment that an
this.x的中期预期付款额
agent makes needs to look like this
代理使需求看起来像这样
it needs to be the agents value for the
它必须是代理商的价值
good x the probability that they get the
好x他们得到的概率
good minus this integral the the
好减去这个积分
integral from zero to VI of this
从零到此的整数
eccentric allocation probability plus
偏心分配概率加
the payment the expected payment that an
付款预期的付款
agent of type zero gets now it's often
现在，类型为零的代理通常
the case that we just want to have
我们只想拥有的情况
auctions in which an agent with the
拍卖与
lowest possible valuation doesn't pay
最低的估值不付钱
anything and if that's true then this
任何事情，如果那是真的，那么这
just goes to zero in the payment
只是零
identity
身份
and we get a slightly simpler expression
我们得到一个稍微简单的表达
but nevertheless this integral probably
但是尽管如此，这个积分可能
seems pretty mysterious to you and
对你来说似乎很神秘，
what's cool about the proof is that I
证明最酷的是，我
can give you a really intuitive idea of
可以给你一个非常直观的想法
where this integral comes from the final
这个积分来自最终
part of the proof that is also really
证明的一部分也确实
interesting is this last statement here
有趣的是，这是最后一条语句
so it says if s is on 2 then the
所以说如果s在2上，那么
converse holds what does that mean
匡威是什么意思
well here we've said that a strategy
在这里，我们已经说过一种策略
profile S is in Bayes Nash equilibrium
轮廓S在贝叶斯纳什均衡中
only if these two conditions hold here
只有这两个条件在这里成立
we're saying if we add the requirement
我们是说如果我们添加要求
that s is on 2 which I'll explain in a
s在2上，我将在
second then it's also sufficient then
第二个就足够了
these two conditions imply base Nash
这两个条件暗示了纳什的基础
equilibrium so what does it mean for us
平衡，这对我们意味着什么
to be on 2 it means there's some type
在2上意味着有某种类型
you could have that would lead you to
你本可以带你去
make any given bid so I can always
进行任何给定的出价，这样我就可以始终
simulate any action that I want to take
模拟我想采取的任何行动
in the game by pretending to have a
在游戏中假装有一个
certain valuation so that means that I
一定的估值，这意味着我
can I can get to any action in the game
我可以在游戏中采取任何行动吗
by having evaluation formally we say the
通过正式评估，我们说
strategy profile is on - that's all that
战略简介已启用-仅此而已
means
手段
so this proof proceeds in three parts
所以这个证明分为三个部分
let me first say this proof follows a
首先让我说这个证明遵循
really elegant proof that I'd like very
我想要的非常优雅的证明
much by Jason Hartline here's a URL to
这是Jason Hartline的很多文章
his book in which he introduces this
他在书中介绍了这一点
proof and I also use figures adapted
证明，我也使用改编的数字
from his proof with his permission so
从他的证明，得到他的允许，所以
this proof has three different parts I'm
这个证明有三个不同的部分
going to start with the last thing I'm
从我最后一件事开始
gonna say that the strategy profile is a
会说策略简介是
Bayes Nash equilibrium if the
如果贝叶斯纳什均衡
monotonicity and payment identity
单调性和付款身份
properties hold and furthermore s is on
属性保持不变，并且s开启
- so I'm going to show that those things
-所以我将展示那些东西
suffice to give us a base Nash
足以给我们基础纳什
equilibrium then I'm gonna show that
平衡，那么我要证明
those two things are necessary that s is
这两件事是必要的
a base Nash equilibrium only when
基本纳什均衡仅当
monotonicity holds and that s is a base
单调性成立并且s是基数
Nash equilibrium only when the payment
纳什均衡只有当支付
identity holds I'll make a couple of
身份持有，我会做几个
simplifying assumptions in this proof
简化此证明中的假设
just to make it a little bit less
只是为了少一点
annoying to follow I'm going to consider
烦人的我要考虑
the special case where the support of
特殊情况下
every agents valuation function is
每个代理商的评估功能是
between 0 and infinity
在0到无穷大之间
so you just have kind of arbitrary
所以你只是有些武断
non-negative real-valued valuations and
非负实值估值和
I'm going to assume that the the payment
我将假设付款
of an agent with type over the lowest
类型超过最低的座席
possible type is zero as I've mentioned
如前所述，可能的类型为零
before okay
没事之前
so moving on to this first part where
所以继续到第一部分
I'm going to show that the
我要证明
characterization and the assumption that
表征和假设
Isis on 2 implies that s is it based at
Isis在2上表示s是基于
equilibrium so to begin if agent I
如果代理人I开始均衡
deviates from taking action from from
从...采取行动
the strategy profile s and instead takes
策略配置文件s而取
the action that the strategy profile
战略概况的行动
asks would have him take if his type was
问他是否要接受他的类型
not VI but instead with some other type
不是VI，而是其他类型
VI hat then what would a jedi's utility
VI帽子那么绝地的效用是什么
be well we can write an expression here
好吧，我们可以在这里写一个表达式
so I'm gonna first of all introduce some
所以我首先要介绍一些
notation I'm going to say I'm gonna use
符号，我要说的是我会用
this notation u sub I comma VI to mean
我用逗号VI表示这个表示法
the utility of an agent I whose real
我的代理人的效用
type is VI when he reports the type of V
他报告V的类型时，类型为VI
hat I and when everyone including him
帽子我，包括他在内的所有人
then follows the strategy profile s and
然后遵循策略配置文件s和
what I mean by him following the
我的意思是他跟随
strategy profile as is that he he kind
策略简介，因为他很友善
of lies to himself he applies the
谎言对他自己适用
strategy profile s to his in correct
他的策略简介正确
type V hat I so so this is kind of the
我是V型帽子，所以这有点
accent from expected utility of agent I
代理商I预期效用的重音
for kind of misreporting his type in the
对于那种在类型中误报他的类型
strategy profile and so what is that
战略概况，那是什么
expected utility well it's the utility
期望的效用是它的效用
that he gets from getting the good - the
他从获得好处中得到-
payment that he has to make so what is
他必须付款的原因是什么
the utility of if he gets from consuming
他从消费中得到的效用
the good well he he gets here I use his
他到达这里的好习惯，我用他的
real valuation because if he actually
实际估值，因为如果他实际上
gets the good he values it according to
得到好的，他根据
his real valuation not according to the
他的实际估值不符合
lie that he told but the probability
他告诉他的谎言，但概率
that he gets the good is going to depend
他得到的好处将取决于
on his declaration so he's going to have
在他的宣言上，所以他将有
the the allocation probability of an
一个人的分配概率
agent with type V hat I but then he's
我有V型帽子的特工，但他是
going to have the utility for getting
将拥有该实用程序
the good of an agent of type VI and his
第六类代理人的利益及其
payment is of course gonna be the
付款当然是
payment of an agent of type V hat I
支付给我V型帽子代理人的费用
because that's what he will have
因为那就是他所拥有的
declared to the mechanism and I note
声明给机制，我注意到
that as I was just saying before it's
就像我刚才说的那样
possible for agent I to play any action
特工我可以采取任何行动
by by behaving in this way because of
通过这样表现
our assumption that S is on too so so by
我们假设S也是如此
you can find some V hat I which will
你可以找到一些V帽我
correspond to any action in the game any
对应游戏中的任何动作
one of the real values in the interval
间隔中的实际值之一
so what does it mean men for a strategy
那么，对于战略男人来说意味着什么
profile asked to be in base nash
要求配置文件为基础纳什
equilibrium
平衡
well it means that agent i is best
好吧，这意味着代理商我是最好的
responding by reporting his true type to
通过报告他的真实类型来回应
his own strategy profile rather than
他自己的策略简介而不是
kind of lying to himself sort of like we
对自己撒谎有点像我们
saw in the revelation principle so in
看到启示的原理，所以在
other words his expected utility for
换句话说，他的预期效用
actually using his true type has to be
实际上使用他的真实类型必须是
at least as big as his expected utility
至少和他预期的效用一样大
for lying to himself and reporting a
对自己撒谎并报告
different type to the strategy profile
与策略配置文件不同的类型
if that's true for all agents and for
如果对所有代理商和
all values that the agent might have and
座席可能具有的所有价值以及
all lies that he might tell then we have
他可能会告诉我们的所有谎言
a base nash equilibria okay well now's
基本的纳什均衡现在好了
the fun part it turns out we can prove
有趣的部分证明我们可以证明
this almost entirely using pictures so
这几乎完全使用图片，所以
let's start by considering some
让我们开始考虑一些
arbitrary and monotonic allocation rule
任意单调分配规则
I mean assume I'm assuming it's
我的意思是假设我假设它是
monotonic because recall the assumption
单调的，因为回忆假设
of our proof is that the
我们的证明是
characterization holds and half of the
表征成立，一半
characterization is that the allocation
表征是分配
rule is monotonic so let's think about
规则是单调的，让我们考虑一下
what this picture says here on the x
这张图片在x上说了什么
axis I have the valuation that an agent
轴我有一个代理商的估值
might have so this is the lowest
可能有，所以这是最低的
possible valuation and this is
可能的估值，这是
infinitely big valuation as we go far
我们走得更远，估值无限大
enough out and what and this is the
足够了，这是什么
probability of getting the good so if
获得利益的可能性，如果
the agent reports the lowest possible
代理报告可能的最低值
valuation
估价
doesn't win the good and because this
不能赢得好处，因为这
rule is monotonic as he reports higher
他报告更高时，规则是单调的
in higher valuations he has an
在较高的估值中，他有一个
increasing chance of getting the good it
获得好处的机会增加
can flatten out and stay level it can go
可以拉平并保持水平
up it can go up gradually it can go up
它可以逐渐上升
just continuously and if it ever hits
只是连续不断，如果有的话
one it has to stay at one because it's
它必须停留在一个，因为它是
monotonic and so the there of course it
单调的，所以当然有
doesn't have to ever hit one it could
不必打一个就可以了
just gradually ramp up but if it ever
只是逐渐增加，但如果有的话
hits one as I've drawn it here and then
我在这里画的时候打了一个
for all values beyond that point it has
对于超出该点的所有值
to stay at one so I'm not gonna make any
留在一个，所以我不会做任何
assumptions about what this function
关于此功能的假设
looks like I accepted that it's
看起来我接受了
monotonic okay
单调还可以
so now let's think about first of all
所以现在让我们首先考虑
agent i's value for consuming the good
代理商我是消费商品的价值
just what i talked about before
就是我之前所说的
remember that his utility has two parts
记住，他的工具有两个部分
his value for consuming the good and the
他在消费商品和
payment that he has to make so first of
他必须先支付的款项
all let's think about his value well as
所有让我们考虑一下他的价值，以及
I argued before this is his value for
我认为这是他的价值所在
telling the truth for for playing
说出玩的真相
truthfully where he he reports his own
说实话他报告自己的地方
true value to the strategy profile and
对战略概况的真正价值
this is his value for consuming the good
这是他消费商品的价值
when he has kind of lied to himself and
当他对自己撒谎时
so he gets a different allocation
所以他得到了不同的分配
probability so let's think about what
概率，所以让我们考虑一下
those things look like on the picture
那些东西看起来像在图片上
well notice that these expressions are
请注意，这些表达式是
products it's a value multiplied by an
产品是价值乘以
allocation probability so we can see
分配概率，所以我们可以看到
that kind of in the picture as a
图片中的那种
rectangle where it's the area of this
这是此区域的矩形
shape here's the valuation right this
形状是这里的估值
distance here is the valuation it goes
这里的距离就是它的估值
from zero to VI and this distance here
从零到VI，这个距离在这里
is the allocation probability it goes
是分配的概率
from zero to X I of VI givenness and so
从零到VI给定的XI等
this whole shaded region here is that
这整个阴影区域是
product so the area of that region is
产品，因此该区域的面积为
the product V I times X I've VI given us
产品VI乘以X我已给我们VI
what about in the case where he doesn't
如果他不这样做怎么办
tell the truth to himself well for this
为此，对自己说实话
proof I'm going to assume that the agent
证明我将假设代理
is considered
被认为
reporting a lower type than his true
报告的类型比他的真实情况低
type you leave it as an exercise for you
输入您将其保留为练习
to do the reverse proof where he
在他做反向证明的地方
considers reporting a higher type but
考虑报告较高的类型，但
it's very much the same argument so it
这是几乎相同的论点，所以
should be easy for you to to check your
应该很容易让您检查您的
understanding by trying to run the proof
通过尝试运行证明来理解
in the other way so when I assume that
换句话说，当我假设
the value V hat I is lower because of my
因为我的价值，我的V帽价值较低
assumption that the function is
假设函数是
monotonic that means that this point
单调的，这意味着这一点
here is going to be lower than this
这将低于这个
point here the pointed V hat I as
指向这里尖的V帽
compared to the pointed V I and so that
比较尖的VI，这样
means that this corresponding point on
表示该对应点在
the y axis is going to be lower than
y轴将低于
this point was over here and all of that
这一点就在这里，所有这些
means that the area of this rectangle
表示此矩形的面积
here is going to be smaller and and it
这将变得更小，它
also means that this this corner of the
也意味着这个角落
rectangle is not going to touch the line
矩形不会碰线
the way that it does here that's fine
这样做的方式很好
okay so so what we've seen so far is
好，所以到目前为止我们所看到的是
we've kind of learned how to look at
我们已经学会了如何看待
these pictures and we've seen that the
这些图片，我们已经看到
area of these two rectangles is the
这两个矩形的面积是
expected utility that the agent gets for
代理获得的预期效用
consuming the good his true value in
消耗商品的真实价值
both cases VI multiplied by the
两种情况VI乘以
allocation probability which depends on
分配概率取决于
whether he's reporting his true type or
他是在报告自己的真实类型还是
reporting some lower type V hat I okay
我报告一些较低的V型帽子
well that's so that was consuming the
那么那是在消耗
good now let's think about the payment
好了，现在让我们考虑付款
that that he has to make to the
他必须对
mechanism well again we're assuming that
再次很好，我们假设
this characterization holds and that
这个特征成立，并且
means that we're assuming that this
表示我们假设
payment identity is true
付款身份为真
I remember the payment identity had a a
我记得付款身份有一个
p0 in here but we don't have to worry
p0在这里，但我们不必担心
about the p0 because what we've assumed
关于p0，因为我们假设
that it's 0 oh pardon me um okay so so
那是0哦，对不起，我很好，所以
what is this so now it's time to think
这是什么，现在该考虑
about this kind of crazy integral so so
关于这种疯狂的积分，所以
how let's actually think about what the
我们如何真正思考
payment identity is well this first term
第一个学期的付款身份很好
here is the one that we've been thinking
这是我们一直在思考的那个
about all along right that's the area of
一直以来，这就是
the rectangle right VI x x
矩形右侧VI xx
VI given s which is that so it's that
VI给出s就是这样
whole shaded region that we just looked
我们刚刚看过的整个阴影区域
at on the previous slide now what are we
现在在上一张幻灯片上，我们是什么
subtracting here this is the integral
在这里减去这是积分
from zero to V I of X I of Z given s so
从零到Z的XI的VI给定s
in other words it's the area underneath
换句话说就是它下面的区域
this allocation curve it's all of that
分配曲线就是全部
so the payment is the whole rectangle
所以付款是整个矩形
minus this stripey region here and of
减去这里和这里的条纹区域
course that's the the gray region that
当然那是灰色地带
I'm showing you on the slide so the
我在幻灯片上向您展示，所以
agents expected payment is the part of
代理商期望的付款是一部分
that rectangle that I showed you which
我给你看的那个矩形
lies above the curve well that's kind of
恰好位于曲线上方
interesting whoops okay so then I can
有趣的呐喊好吧，那么我可以
put those two things together and figure
将这两件事放在一起并计算
out what the agents expected utility is
找出代理商期望的效用
for playing as though his type was VI
就像他的类型是VI
and playing as though his type was VI
好像他的类型是VI
hat given that in fact his type really
考虑到实际上他的类型
is VI and so well remember that the
是VI，所以请记住
expression for this expected utility is
此预期效用的表达式是
simply the value for consuming the good
仅仅是消费商品的价值
which as we saw before whoops is the
正如我们在呐喊之前所看到的
rectangle minus the payment identity
矩形减去付款身份
which as we saw before is the part of
正如我们之前所见，这是
the rectangle that lives above the line
线上方的矩形
and so this difference then is the area
所以这个差异就是面积
that lies below the line so that's the
它位于线下，所以
amount of utility that the agent would
代理会产生的效用数量
get and you can see that these two
得到，你可以看到这两个
pictures are pretty similar they're
图片非常相似
they're both this area under the curve
他们都是曲线下的这个区域
they both go up to VI but the difference
他们俩都升至VI，但差异
is that this one kind of gets clipped
是这种被剪裁的
off at this lower allocation probability
以较低的分配概率关闭
here which we kind of correspond to
在这里我们有点对应
about here whereas this one goes a bit
在这里，而这个有点
higher and indeed if I then think about
更高，如果我再考虑
the utility difference the the utility
效用差异效用
then the difference in utility between
那么效用之间的差异
telling telling the truth really playing
讲真话实话
as as the TrueType and
与TrueType和
the utility of playing as though you had
仿佛您玩过的实用程序
a different type that's going to be this
不同的类型将是这样
amount here and what's important the
数量在这里，重要的是
thing that we have done all of this in
我们已经完成了所有这些工作的事情
order to reason to ourselves is that
为了推理自己是
this is a positive number and the fact
这是一个正数，事实
that it is an actual area in our graph
这是我们图中的实际区域
that it has positive area goes to show
它有积极的领域去表明
that it's a positive number and because
这是一个正数，因为
of monotonicity really the result that
单调性的结果
made this true is that this point here
做到这一点是这里
has to be weakly lower than this point
必须弱于此点
here it would have been possible for the
在这里，对于
function to be flat here in that region
在该区域的功能保持平坦
and if it was then this number would be
如果是，那么这个数字将是
zero rather than being positive but it
零而不是积极的，但它
can never be negative the only way that
永远不会否定的唯一方式
it could be negative would be if the
这可能是负面的，如果
function went down and the function is
功能下降，功能是
not allowed to go down by monotonicity
不允许单调下降
and so so that tells us that this
因此，这告诉我们
utility difference is always going to be
效用差异永远是
non-negative and remember we argued
非负的，记得我们争论过
before that as long as this number is
在此之前，只要这个数字是
greater than or equal to this number
大于或等于此数字
then s is a based on Calibri and so what
那么s是基于Calibri的，那么
we've just argued is that indeed that's
我们只是在争论那确实是
true so so the characterisation plus our
是的，所以特征加上我们的
assumption that s is on - allows us to
假设s开启-允许我们
reason that s is a base nash equilibrium
s是基础纳什均衡的原因
so that's a really powerful thing we've
所以这是我们真正强大的一件事
just seen something very structural
刚刚看到一些非常结构化的东西
about what the base nash equilibrium of
关于什么基础纳什均衡
a quasi linear mechanism has to look
拟线性机制必须看
like ok now let's do the sufficient
好的，现在让我们做足够的
conditions so now i want to say that s
条件，所以现在我想说
being a base nash equilibrium implies
作为基础纳什均衡意味着
that monotonicity has to hold ok so so
单调性必须保持不变
again I'm going to make the same kind of
再次，我将做同样的
argument that I made before that having
我在那之前提出的论点
a base nash equilibrium implies that for
基本纳什均衡意味着
all valuations that the agents could
代理商可以进行的所有估值
have and all other valuations that they
以及他们拥有的所有其他估值
could pretend to have the utility that
可能假装具有该实用程序
agent i gets on expectation from really
代理商，我真的期望
having valuation VI and playing as
具有估值VI并以
though he has valuation VI is at least
尽管他的估值VI至少是
as big as the utility that he gets from
和他从中获得的效用一样大
really having valuation VI and playing
真正拥有估值VI并玩
like he has valuation
就像他有估值
i prime if I expand this out I get this
如果我将其扩展，我会得到
expression here here all that I've done
在这里表达我所做的一切
is just substituted in this expression
在此表达式中被替换
that we already looked at in the
我们已经在
previous part of the proof that says
证明的前一部分
that my utility is the the amount that I
我的效用就是我的金额
get by consuming the good - the payment
通过消耗商品获得-付款
that I have to make in both cases
在两种情况下我都必须做的
depending on the report that I really
取决于我的报告
made okay so so you may have noticed
一切正常，所以您可能已经注意到
I've switched from using V hat to V
我已经从使用V帽切换到了V
prime and that's because I want to
素，那是因为我想
actually think that that this has to be
实际上认为这必须是
it can be possible for the agent really
代理商真的有可能
to have valuation VI or really to have
拥有估值VI或真正具有
valuation VI prime and I can use these
估值VI素数，我可以使用这些
these facts both ways so I'm going to
这些事实都是双向的，所以我要
consider two possible values z1 and z2
考虑两个可能的值z1和z2
that the agent really could have and I'm
那个经纪人真的可以拥有的，我是
gonna substitute in to this expression
将替代这个表达
here kind of both ways so I'm going to
这两种方式，所以我要
substitute in VI equals Z one VI prime
VI中的替代值等于Z一个VI质数
equals z2 and I'm also going to
等于z2，我也要
substitute in the other way around and
用另一种方式替代
depending on which way I substitute I
取决于我替代我的方式
get two different inequalities so if I
得到两个不等式，所以如果我
do the first substitution here then I
在这里做第一次替换
get this inequality which says well it
得到这个不等式
says what you read there's no point am I
说你读的书我没有意义
reading it out but but it gives an
读出来，但它给
expression that that has z2 here and Zed
Z2在这里和Zed的表达式
one here for example when I do things
例如当我做某事时
the other way around everything switches
反过来一切都切换
so I get Zed ones and said twos in the
所以我得到了Zed并在
other way and and both times I have the
反过来说，两次我都有
inequality pointing this way because
不平等之所以这样指出，是因为
that's that's what we always started out
那就是我们一开始就做的
with so so basically what this is saying
基本上这么说
is an agent of type Zed one wouldn't
是Zed类型的代理，不会
want to lie and pretend to have type z2
想要撒谎并假装具有类型z2
and similarly an agent of type z2
同样是z2类型的代理
wouldn't want to lie and pretend to have
不想撒谎和假装有
type said one either
类型说一个
okay well I've got these two different
好吧，我有这两种不同
inequalities here so I can just add them
不平等在这里，所以我可以添加它们
together and if I do that then that
在一起，如果我这样做，那
causes these P terms to cancel out and
使这些P项抵消并
so then I just get these two things
所以我就得到这两件事
added together and when I do that I end
加在一起，当我这样做时，我结束
up with
与
this expression here and then I can just
这种表达在这里，然后我就可以
factor that expression and I end up with
因素的表达，我最终与
this simpler inequality here that
这里的不等式
doesn't talk about the payments at all
根本不谈论付款
and I
和我
you can verify that for yourself that's
您可以亲自验证
just some simple algebraic manipulation
只是一些简单的代数运算
and really the monotonicity requirement
真正的单调性要求
just pops directly out of this
只是直接从中弹出
expression here so in particularly you
在这里表达，尤其是你
can see that if Z 2 is bigger than Z 1
可以看到Z 2是否大于Z 1
meaning that this term here is positive
表示这里的这个词是肯定的
then in order for this inequality to be
那么为了使这种不平等成为
true in order for this whole thing to be
为了使整个事情成为真
non-negative we have to make sure that
非负的，我们必须确保
this is also not negative so we can
这也不是负面的，所以我们可以
conclude that this being positive
得出结论，这是积极的
implies that this has to be positive
暗示这必须是积极的
oh sorry mistake on the slide I should
哦，抱歉，幻灯片上的错误我应该
say is positive so I'll change that in
说是肯定的，所以我将改变它
the slides so in other words it means
幻灯片，换句话说，这意味着
that the x function has to be monotone
x函数必须是单调的
non-decreasing it means that when when
不减少意味着什么时候
this number is bigger than this number
这个数字大于这个数字
this number has to be bigger than this
这个数字必须大于这个
number so that means the function has to
数字，这意味着该功能必须
be weakly going up and that's that's
虚弱地上升，那就是
exactly what monotonicity says so that
确切地说，单调性是这样的
establishes this second part of the
建立了第二部分
proof all right so now there's only one
证明没事，所以现在只有一个
last thing to say and that is that this
最后要说的是
payment identity is is required so so
要求提供付款身份，所以
let's see what I want to say here is
让我们看看我想说的是
that the strategy profile is a Bayes
战略概况是贝叶斯
Nash equilibrium implies that we need
纳什均衡意味着我们需要
the payment identity the payment vanity
付款身份付款虚荣
didn't just kind of suffice to give us a
不仅仅是给我们一个机会
basic Nash equilibrium but we actually
基本的纳什均衡，但实际上
need to have it so I'm gonna start with
需要它，所以我要开始
those same two inequalities that we just
我们刚才提到的两个不等式
talked about before and now I'm going to
谈到以前，现在我要
do something different I'm gonna solve
做一些我要解决的事情
each of them for this expression so I'm
他们每个人都为此表达，所以我
going to kind of rearrange them you
要重新安排他们你
notice they both have a P I said to
注意他们两个都有一个PI
given
给定
and @p I said one given s and so if I
和@p我说了一个给定的s，所以如果我
rearrange things then I can I can get
重新整理事情，然后我可以得到
them so they both have that on one side
他们，所以他们都在一侧
of the expression and when I do that I
的表达，当我这样做时
end up with one of the equations looking
最终得到其中一个方程式
one of the inequalities looking like
看起来像不平等之一
this and the other one looking like that
这个和另一个看起来像那样
and in total I can think of that as
总的来说，我可以认为是
upper and lower bounds on the
上限和下限
differences in expected payments that
预期付款的差异
have to be made between agents of type Z
必须在Z型代理之间进行
2 and agents of type said 1 so in other
2，其他类型的代理说1
words this difference in payments whoops
用词表达这种支付差异
this difference in payments here has to
这里的付款差异必须
be not less than this amount and not
不小于此数量且不小于
more than this amount well that's fine
超过这个数量就可以了
but this just looks like a lot of messy
但这看起来很乱
math it's not clear why these upper and
数学尚不清楚为什么这些高和
lower bounds are very helpful to me well
下限对我很有帮助
here again we want to go back to our
再次在这里，我们想回到我们的
pictures so let's visualize this on the
图片，所以让我们在
graphs that we were looking at before so
我们以前看过的图形
so here I've just written the upper and
所以在这里我只写了上部
lower bound expression for you again so
下界表达式再次为您
that you can compare it and here is the
您可以比较它，这是
upper bound and here is the lower bound
上限，这是下限
and let's think about what those numbers
让我们考虑一下这些数字
mean well here I'm multiplying by Z 2 so
意思是这里我要乘以Z 2
here's the distance Z 2 and here I have
这是距离Z 2，我有
the allocation probability of an agent
代理人的分配概率
of type Z 2 minus the allocation
Z 2的类型减去分配
probability for an agent of types that
一个类型的主体的概率
one and that's this difference here and
一个，就是这里的区别，
so in total the upper bound is this
所以总的来说上限是
shaded region here so the payment
这里的阴影区域，所以付款
difference can be no more than that
差异不能超过
the lower bound is Z 1 multiplied by
下限是Z 1乘以
that same difference so I have that same
同样的差异，所以我也一样
difference that I had before now
我以前有过的不同
multiplied by Z 1 so that gives me this
乘以Z 1，所以给我这个
shaded region and the important thing to
阴影区域和重要的是
notice about these two
关于这两个的注意
regions is that they intersect the curve
区域是它们与曲线相交
at different points so this one touches
在不同的地方，所以这一点感动
the curve right there and this one
那里的曲线和这一个
touches the curve right there well I can
我可以很好地触及曲线
argue this more formally using calculus
用微积分更正式地争论这一点
but if you think about it it's easy to
但是如果您考虑一下，这很容易
get an intuition that makes it clearer
得到直觉，使之更清晰
but the only payment rule that can
但唯一可以
satisfy these upper and lower bounds for
满足以下上限和下限
every given pair of types is said 1 and
每个给定的类型对都说1和
Z 2 has payment difference that's equal
Z 2的付款差额相等
exactly to the shaded region that's
恰好是阴影区域
shown here basically it needs to touch
这里显示基本上需要触摸
the curve everywhere because if I change
曲线无处不在，因为如果我改变
that 1 and Z 2 I still need to have the
那1和Z 2我仍然需要
problem the property that it's never
质疑从未有过的财产
less so it's never more than that amount
更少，所以永远不会超过这个数量
and it's never less than that amount and
而且永远不会少于那个数量
so as I kind of move around I need to
所以当我四处走动时，我需要
make sure that I always have those sort
确保我总是有那种
of points of contact with the curve and
与曲线的接触点
the only way for that to work everywhere
使其在任何地方工作的唯一方法
is to have contact with the curve
与曲线接触
everywhere so kind of in an intuitive
到处都是如此直观
level that that should be convincing to
应该说服的水平
you and if you'd like to see the the
您，如果您想查看
proof with calculus you can look at the
用微积分证明，你可以看看
the book citation that I gave you at the
我给你的那本书的引文
beginning and that pretty much gives us
开始，这几乎给了我们
the payment identity in order to get the
付款身份以获取
payment identity we just want to set Z 1
我们只想设置Z 1的付款身份
equals 0 so push this guy all the way
等于0，所以一直推这个家伙
down said said 2 equals 1 and then that
向下说2等于1然后
gives us this whole shaded region that
给我们整个阴影区域
we saw before ok so that concludes our
我们在确定之前就看到了，因此可以得出结论
proof of the the base Nash equilibrium
基本纳什均衡的证明
characterization result and recall that
表征结果并回顾
that that directly gives us the revenue
直接给我们带来收入
equivalence theorem as a corollary
等价定理作为推论
because would revel in the revenue
因为会带来收益
equivalence theorem said is that having
等价定理说的是
the same allocation probability implies
相同的分配概率意味着
having and also having the same payment
也有相同的付款
for an agent with the lowest possible
对于尽可能低的代理商
type implies having the same expected
类型意味着期望值相同
payments what this characterization
支付此特征
result said is it's something much
结果说是很多
stronger that having the same allocation
具有相同分配的更强
probability implies exactly the the
概率恰好暗示了
payment
付款
that you saw and the payment identity
您看到的以及付款身份
has determinant for what the the lowest
有最低的决定因素
possible type gets and so if that is set
可能的类型获取，因此如果已设置
constant and in both cases then then
常数，然后在两种情况下
they have to be the same so so the
他们必须一样，所以
overall claim that we want to make here
我们要在这里提出的总体主张
that overall take away from all of this
总体上消除了所有这些
is that if two mechanisms have the same
是如果两种机制具有相同的
allocation rule then they basically have
分配规则，那么他们基本上有
the same payment rule too and when I say
同样的付款规则，当我说
basically essentially all I really mean
基本上我真正要说的是
is that the only thing that can change
是唯一可以改变的东西
is if I just offset everything by a
是如果我只是用一个偏移量
constant so if I pay you $100 for
不变，所以如果我付给您$ 100
showing up in my auction and then we
出现在我的拍卖中，然后我们
have an auction then my expected revenue
进行拍卖，然后获得我的预期收入
is different you know if I charge you
不一样，你知道我是否要收费
$100 for walking in the door and you
$ 100即可进门，而您
have no choice about whether to walk in
别无选择
the door and then we have an auction
门，然后我们进行拍卖
I'll get a different amount of revenue
我会得到不同的收入
but that's not very satisfying that's
但这不是很令人满意
why we have this requirement about the
为什么我们对
agent with the lowest possible type gets
具有最低可能类型的业务代表
paid zero as long as that's true then
只要是真的就支付零
there's really no other wiggle room in
真的没有其他摆动空间
the payment rule and so mechanisms with
付款规则等机制
the same allocation rule just need to
相同的分配规则只需要
have the same payment rule a key
具有相同的付款规则
corollary is that all efficient auctions
结果是所有有效的拍卖
yield the same revenue in equilibrium
平衡产生相同的收入
because after all efficiency is just one
因为毕竟效率只是一个
allocation rule right efficiency means
分配规则权效率手段
the agent with the highest valuation
估价最高的代理商
always gets the good that's an example
总是得到好处，这就是一个例子
of a restriction of what the allocation
限制什么分配
rule needs to be and so so that tells us
规则必须如此，这样才能告诉我们
that it turns out most of the options we
事实证明，大多数选择
care about are efficient and so for all
关心是有效的，所以对所有人
of these efficient auctions we know that
在这些有效的拍卖中，我们知道
there's actually nothing we can do to
实际上我们无能为力
get to change the amount of revenue that
改变收入的数额
we get an equilibrium by changing the
我们通过改变
option within efficient auctions and
有效拍卖中的选择权，以及
indeed this applies not just to the
确实，这不仅适用于
auctions we've seen before
我们之前看过的拍卖
but to some pretty weird auction so you
但是要进行一些非常奇怪的拍卖，
can think about not a first or second
不能考虑第一或第二
price auction but a third price auction
价格拍卖，但第三次价格拍卖
and that actually turns out to be
事实证明是
revenue equivalent you can think about
您可以考虑的收入等值
various auction designs in which not
各种拍卖设计，其中没有
only the winners have to pay but losers
只有胜利者必须付出，但失败者
pay too we didn't make any assumptions
付钱也没做任何假设
about these kinds of things in the proof
关于证明中的这类事情
and so it turns out they're also revenue
所以事实证明他们也是收益
equivalent one last caveat risk
等效的最后警告风险
neutrality did turn out to be important
中立确实很重要
so I've assumed everywhere in this video
所以我在这个视频中到处都有
that agents are risk neutral which means
代理商是风险中性的，这意味着
they treat expected payments the same as
他们将预期付款与
worth in payments they don't care about
值得他们不在乎的付款
how much randomness there is in the
有多少随机性
environment they just care about the
他们只是在乎的环境
expected payment they have to make and
他们必须支付的预期付款和
if that isn't true then these are
如果那不是真的，那么这些是
different auction mechanisms actually do
实际上有不同的拍卖机制
turn out to be different so so that
事实证明是不同的
concludes this lecture and you'll go on
结束本讲座，您将继续
now in the next lecture to think about
现在在下一个讲座中考虑
how to actually maximize revenue in an
如何在
auction and where we can see from today
拍卖以及我们今天可以看到的地方
is that's gonna have to happen by
那将是必须发生的
changing the allocation rule there's no
更改分配规则没有
way of maximizing with inefficiency
效率低下的最大化方式
because efficient auctions are all going
因为有效的拍卖都在进行
to yield the same revenues so if what
产生相同的收入，如果
you want to do is to maximize your
你想做的就是最大化你的
revenue
收入
strangely enough you you are gonna turn
奇怪的是你要转身
out not to want to sell to the person
不想卖给那个人
with the highest valuation all the time
一直以来估值最高